city-data.com 2009-03-28

# Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that Advameg, Inc. (“Service Provider,” “we” or “our”) collects and uses the personally identifiable information garnered through our website, www.city-data.com (“Website”). It is our goal to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.

## **THE TYPE OF INFORMATION THE WEBSITE COLLECTS**

Personally identifiable information is collected by the Website with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, register for our forum or business profile, you maybe be asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name, or phone number. Optional information such as your age or gender may also be requested. By submitting such web form contained on this Website, you agree to the processing and storage of your information by the Service Provider.

If you contact us by email through the Website, we reserve the right to also keep a record of the email itself and any personally identifiable information provided in that email and any others that result, in order to respond to them and for any other purpose described in this Policy.

Our servers may also automatically collect information about your computer when you visit the Website, including without limitation the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, date and time of the visit, the website that referred you, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. Your IP address is usually associated with your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university, and may identify your physical location.

## **DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We generally do not disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties. However, we reserve the right to disclose this information if we reasonably believe it is needed for any of the following reasons:  
1\. Pursuant to a subpoena or other governmental request  
2\. For any other reason required by law  
3\. In order to protect our employees, independent contractors, affiliates, the users of this Website or the public at large and their property, rights and safety  
4\. To enforce any terms of service on this Website  
5\. To provide you with the services or products requested by you

Your personally identifiable information may also be disclosed, without limitation, if the Service Provider is acquired or in the event of any sale or transfer of assets of the Service Provider.

We use the personally identifiable information that we receive to contact you about your requests to us. We may also, from time to time, send you information that we feel that you might be interested in. 

We will use your information only as permitted by law. Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. As one example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive. Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners, but cannot be used to contact you individually.

## **USE OF COOKIES**

Website may use "cookies," Flash objects or similar electronic tools to collect information, such as the IP address of your computer, to enhance and customize your experience with this Website. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer and which collects information about your use of this Website, such as the Web pages visited, the date and the time of a visit, the Web sites you visited immediately before, etc. Cookies may be stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Cookies served by our Website do not gather demographic information about our users. Cookies may also be used to provide our advertisers with targeted advertising opportunities, and advertising vendors that serve ads on our Website may also use their own cookies. You may choose not to accept any cookies from any party by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of our Website may not function properly.

## **SURVEYS AND CONTESTS**

From time-to-time, our Website requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose any information. 

## **HOW THE WEBSITE USES INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU**

We may use personally identifying information you supply through the Website to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you subscribe to our forum, we may use your e-mail address to send you periodic e-mails. Similarly, if you enter an online sweepstakes, we will use this information to notify you if you are a winner. If you do not wish to receive future commercial communications from us by e-mail, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail.

We also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance or forums and job search software, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. We reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times contain sufficient information for us to be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our Website. 

We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 

As our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by the Service Provider, its parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and/or about our Website users may be among the transferred assets. 

## **AFFILIATED SITES, LINKED SITES AND ADVERTISEMENTS**

We expect our partners, advertisers and third-party affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. However, third parties, including our business partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our Website, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visits to our Website you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a Website page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through a page on the Website you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, advertisements, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. We are not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our Website, our advertisers, business partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising may be served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Through features available on our Website, third parties may use cookies or other technology to gather information. We do not control the use of this technology or the resulting information and are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

Our Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Website and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

## **CHILDREN**

This Website is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums and chats. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. 

## **SECURITY**

Because no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable, Service Provider can not guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers or databases, and by using the Website you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you use the Website. We take precautions to protect your personally identifiable information but no computer system is completely secure. Due to this, we cannot guarantee the safety of your personally identifiable information.  In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you. If notification is appropriate, we may notify you by e-mail (provided we have your e-mail address). 

## CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our Website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

## **GOVERNING LAW**

This policy and the use of this Website are governed by Illinois law. The exclusive jurisdiction for any claim, dispute, or litigation (“Litigation”) arising out of the operation of the Website or this policy shall be vested in the federal and state courts located in Chicago, Cook County, Illinois, and such courts shall have exclusive jurisdiction over the parties and the subject matter of any such Litigation. You hereby agree to consent to and hereby waive all arguments or claims regarding venue for such Litigation.  If Service Provider prevails in such Litigation it shall be entitled to collect from you all costs incurred by it in the Litigation including reasonable attorneys’ fees and the cost of investigation. If you are located outside the United States, please note the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. You hereby consent to this transfer.

In the event of any conflict between the terms of this policy and the terms of any electronic or machine readable privacy policy (for example, a P3P electronic privacy policy), the terms of this policy shall control. 

## CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us using the Contact Us page of this Website.
